These Foreign-only subtitles ver. 2024-10 were created by ZoowlCZ.
[Quenya] Aiya Eärendil, Elenion Ancalima!
[English] Hail Eärendil, Brightest of the Stars!
[Black Speech]  Kelkum-ishi.
[English]  In the coldness.
[Black Speech]  Ash nazg durb!
[English]  One Ring to rule!
[Quenya] ♫ Et Eärello... ♫
[English] ♫ Out of the Great Sea... ♫
[Quenya] ♫ ...Endorenna utúlien. ♫
[English] ♫ ...to Middle-earth I am come. ♫
[Quenya] ♫ Sinome maruvan... ♫
[English] ♫ In this place I will abide... ♫
[Quenya] ♫ ...ar Hildinyar... ♫
[English] ♫ ...and my heirs... ♫
[Quenya] ♫ ...tenn’ Ambar-metta. ♫
[English] ♫ ...unto the World-ending. ♫
[Sindarin] Hannon le.
[English] Thank you.
[Sindarin] ♫ Tinúviel... ♫
[English] ♫ Tinúviel... ♫
[Sindarin] ♫ ...elvanui... ♫
[English] ♫ ...the elven-fair... ♫
[Sindarin] ♫ ...elleth alfirin edhelhael. ♫
[English] ♫ ...immortal maiden elven-wise. ♫
[Sindarin] I Aear cân ven na mar.
[English] The sea calls us to home.